<data>
  <lang id="en_US">
    <section id="common">
      <text id="looted">I've already looted this!</text>
      <text id="mine_lab">Miner's Lab</text>
      <text id="mine_silo">Silo</text>
      <text id="asteroids_end">You have reached the end of Asteroids for this update.</text>
    </section>
    <section id="system">
      <text id="wormhole">Uncharted System</text>
    </section>
    <section id="system.desc">
      <text id="wormhole">There are no known records of this place through the wyrmhole.</text>
    </section>
    <section id="system.planet">
      <text id="asteroids">Asteroid Field</text>
      <text id="smastirini">ESA-Smastirini</text>
      <text id="hq_battlefield">Fleet Battle</text>
    </section>
    <section id="system.planet.desc">
      <text id="asteroids">Due to it's ever shifting nature, this unrealisticaly packed asteroid field is never the same twice!</text>
      <text id="uamt.asteroids">Due to it's ever shifting nature, this unrealisticaly packed asteroid field is never the same twice!</text>
      <text id="smastirini">No navigation data.</text>
      <text id="asteroids.solar_system">Once a great mining location, now full of debris from Earth's armies.</text>
      <text id="asteroids.hq_battlefield">Aid humanity on the front lines of the war!</text>
      <text id="wormhole.asteroids">A lone rocky belt around an empty star.</text>
    </section>
    <section id="item.names">
      <text id="utility_ship">Utility Ship</text>
      <text id="utility_ship_gun">Utility Ship Gun</text>
      <text id="utility_ship_laser">Utility Ship Laser</text>
      <text id="utility_droid">Utility Droid</text>
      <text id="advanced_tech">Advanced Tech</text>
      <text id="fighter.bomb">Bomb Launcher</text>
      <text id="fighter.beam">Plasma Beam</text>
      <text id="fighter.mine">Mining Beam</text>
      <text id="antimatter_bomb">Antimatter Bomb</text>
      <text id="matter_bomb">Fighter Bomb</text>
      <text id="asteroid_scanner">Asteroid Field Scanner</text>
      <text id="temporal_crystal">Temporal Crystal</text>
    </section>
    <section id="item.descriptions">
      <text id="utility_ship">An ATV with heavy shields and spaceflight capability!</text>
      <text id="utility_droid">All-purpose combat droid.</text>
      <text id="fighter.mine">[tile=power]Power per Item: 100 \n Mines and collects Items.</text>
      <text id="temporal_crystal">Strange patterns flicker across its surface, and it seems not entirely of this reality.</text>
      <text id="asteroid_scanner">Allows you to search an asteroid field for a specific biome.</text>
    </section>
    <section id="npc">
      <text id="space_miner">Space Miner</text>
      <text id="space_miner_captain">Space Miner Captain</text>
    </section>
    <section id="structure.tooltip">
      <text id="mine_lab">Craft in Miner's Lab</text>
      <text id="mine_silo">Enter Silo</text>
    </section>
    <section id="quests">
      <text id="find_smastirini">Distress Signal</text>
      <text id="find_space_pirates">Space Pirates</text>
      <text id="get_adv_tech">Advanced Tech</text>
      <text id="space_miners">Find Materials</text>
      <text id="mine_beam">New Tech</text>
    </section>
    <section id="quest.description">
      <text id="find_smastirini">Investigate the distress signal.</text>
      <text id="find_space_pirates">wants you to find and eliminate Space Pirates.</text>
      <text id="get_adv_tech">requests some materials for new technology.</text>
      <text id="space_miners">needs materials for new weapons.</text>
      <text id="mine_beam">needs materials for new mining tech.</text>
    </section>
    <section id="empty_space">
      <text id="first_visit">This is weird. There is a completely empty patch of space in the middle of the field...</text>
      <text id="first_visit2">Something feels off, but I can't put my finger on it.</text>
      <text id="next_visit">This empty space again, taunting me...</text>
    </section>
    <section id="awreck_logs">
      <text id="distress">I'm picking up a distress signal from this area! I must investigate!</text>
      <text id="awreck_log1">We c@me here to test these new drones. Thay were said t0 be faii proof.</text>
      <text id="awreck_log2">They se&med to work. But th#n... They turn*d on us.</text>
      <text id="awreck_log3">We don'.. know f%om w^re. But they came. An.. they des&r..yed us. We h$& n.. ch*n@#</text>
      <text id="awreck_read">I've already read this. I know how it ends...</text>
      <text id="smastirini1">The rest of this log is too corrupted to read. I wonder if those droids are still around...</text>
      <text id="smastirini2">These logs suggest this ship was part of a larger mission...</text>
      <text id="smastirini3">I am picking up a distress signal! I wonder if there might still be survivors...</text>
      <text id="smastirini4">No signs of life... This signal must have been sent long ago...</text>
      <text id="smastirini5">These are the logs of the Research Vessel the ESA-Smastirini. Our mission was simple: field testing of new remote operations drones.</text>
      <text id="smastirini6">At first, all seemed well. But as we recieved scanner reports, we discovered something had gone terribly wrong. We had somehow mis-jumped, an impossibility as according to known science.</text>
      <text id="smastirini7">We began to fear... but nothing seemed out of the ordinary. We started testing our drones... and then it all went wrong.</text>
      <text id="smastirini8">On day 3, the first ship disappeared. One moment it was there, the next it was gone. Someone gave Them a name... the unseen force opposing us.</text>
      <text id="smastirini9">On day 8, we had harvested enough [item=exotic_matter] for the jump back. But when we engaged the engines, nothing happened. And then all went to hell.</text>
      <text id="smastirini10">The drones turned on us. They destroyed us. Some of our ships may have been able to get away, but I find that possibility unlikely...</text>
      <text id="smastirini11">I can hear them coming now... Goodbye... I hope this log serves as warning to any who may come after...</text>
      <text id="ambush1">These people have been long dead... so who sent the signal?</text>
      <text id="ambush2">It was a trap! The signal was a fake! I must get out of here!</text>
      <text id="give_utility_droid">It seems this ship specialized in drones. Most of the data is corrupted but I can still extract the plans for an [item=utility_droid]!</text>
      <text id="loot_jumpship">I was able to scavenge a jumpship from the debris.</text>
      <text id="repair_smastirini">The ship has been destroyed beyond repair.</text>
    </section>
    <section id="space_pirates">
      <text id="get_utility_ship">I was able to extract the plans for the pirate's ships. I should be able to make my own now!</text>
      <text id="pirates1">I see you found an [color=770000]Asteroid Field[/color]! I have checked your ship's scanner logs and they picked up activity in the area.</text>
      <text id="pirates2">I have reason to suspect it is pirates. Let me just run some tests... [pause=1]Aha! I have locked onto a signal from the pirates' base!</text>
      <text id="pirates3">If you can go and eradicate them, I might be able to make something out of their tech!</text>
      <text id="pirates4">I have killed the pirates the [object=mechanic] asked for... I'll call her on the [item=com_device].</text>
      <text id="pirates5">Cass? I killed the pirates you asked.</text>
      <text id="pirates6">Great! Can you search their base for some [item=advanced_tech] and bring it to me?</text>
      <text id="pirates7">Here's the tech you wanted.</text>
      <text id="pirates8">Awesome! I can make so much new tech with this! Go check out the new recipes in the [color=770000]Advanced Lab[/color]!</text>
      <text id="explore_more">I would recommend going back to the [color=770000]Asteroid Field[/color] and seeing if you can find anything else!</text>
    </section>
    <section id="space_miners">
      <text id="no_entry">Hey! Get out of there!</text>
      <text id="gather_stuff1">Hello there Traveler! Could you spare some time to help us?</text>
      <text id="gather_stuff2">The pirates in the vicinity keep attacking our operations. We require some materials to repair our defense systems.</text>
      <text id="gather_stuff3">If you could obtain some of the pirate's tech, we might be able to fight them off.</text>
      <text id="gather_stuff4">Amazing! I will use this to craft some new tech in our [color=770000]Lab[/color]! Feel free to use our facilities as you please!</text>
      <text id="mine_beam1">We have been developing a new laser beam, but it requires large amounts of [item=magnegem]s to complete. Could you get some?</text>
      <text id="mine_beam2">This is exactly what we need! Feel free to craft a [item=fighter.mine] in the [color=770000]Lab[/color]!</text>
      <text id="thanks">Thank you for all your help, traveller! Feel free to borrow any resources you need!</text>
      <text id="destroyed">The pirates must have destroyed this base... I'll see what I can salvage from the poor miners...</text>
      <text id="com_device">You can call us on your [item=com_device] to find your way back here if needed.</text>
      <text id="call1">Greetings Traveler! I am transmitting our location now...</text>
      <text id="call2">.[pause=3].[pause=3].[pause=3] Location transmitted! We await your return!</text>
    </section>
    <section id="asteroid_scanner">
      <text id="not_asteroid_field">Error: Not an asteroid field!</text>
      <text id="choose_field">Select a biome to search for:</text>
      <text id="biome_selected">A suitable biome has been located. The next time you enter this asteroid field, that biome will generate.</text>
      <text id="crystal_full">The [item=temporal_crystal] is still completely intact.</text>
      <text id="no_crystal">You do not have any [item=temporal_crystal]s!</text>
    </section>
    <section id="actions">
      <text id="scan_asteroid_field">Scan Asteroid Field</text>
      <text id="replace_crystal">Replace Crystal</text>
    </section>
    <section id="wormhole">
      <text id="exit_field">You try to leave, but end up right where you were, feeling like you never left...</text>
      <text id="lo_alien_hit">[font=drachenklaue]what the fuck man?!?[/font]</text>
    </section>
  </lang>
</data>
